<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Updates on Naftiko Go-To-Market</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Updates on Naftiko Go-To-Market</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/docs/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello Community</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/blog/2026/01/06/hello-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/blog/2026/01/06/hello-community/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the go-to-market site for Naftiko. It provides the entire blueprint for how Naftiko conducts marketing and evangelism. Like our market research, technology, and revenue site we don&amp;rsquo;t see any reason why we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be doing all this work out in the open and sharing with the community as we progress&amp;ndash;allowing others to learn from, join in, making the go-to-market motion a community thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I use the YAML for capabilities, channels, events, glossary, organizations, services, standards, stories, and use cases in this Docsy site hosted on GitHub to manage all the ideas and activities I am setting in motion on any given day. I use the issues for the repo as an inbox, submitting ideas as I move fast through a variety of conversations and content work. Feel free to jump and use anything here, as I continue to execute our GTM motion, automate a lot of what I do, and work to amplify Naftiko, but also the open-source stanards and tooling we are building on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up YouTube, Apple, and Spotify Podcasts for Naftiko Capabilities</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/blog/2026/01/06/setting-up-youtube-apple-and-spotify-podcasts-for-naftiko-capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/blog/2026/01/06/setting-up-youtube-apple-and-spotify-podcasts-for-naftiko-capabilities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I spent a couple of hours setting up the minimum viable channels needed to support the Naftiko Podcast out of the gate. It was interesting to see the difference in user experience between YouTube, Apple, and Spotify. YouTube is definitely the most advanced. I like the Apple one because it is 100% configured by an RSS feed for the podcast, which has it&amp;rsquo;s ups and downs. Spotify was by far the worst experience, with the interface spinning wheel never stopping and every other API call failing behind the scenes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/blog/2025/11/04/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/blog/2025/11/04/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the go-to-market documentation site for Naftiko. It contains all of the stories, conversations, and channels we will be publishing to. It provides an ongoing snaprshot of our go-to-market function, providing a blueprint for me to follow when getting the word out about what we are building at Naftiko, and once we have a product to put in the hands of developers, we&amp;rsquo;ll already have this machine broken in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
